<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sarah Salter</title>
    <link>/./</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sarah Salter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/./index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope This Works</title>
      <link>/./post/hope-this-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./post/hope-this-works/</guid>
      <description>Post About Cars colnames(cars) ## [1] &amp;quot;speed&amp;quot; &amp;quot;dist&amp;quot; hist(cars$speed) Hoping that this will print.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Post</title>
      <link>/./post/new-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./post/new-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Manipulation with DPLYR</title>
      <link>/./blog/2018-02-18-dplyr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./blog/2018-02-18-dplyr/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Dplyr Dplyr is an R package, designed for the purpose of manipulating data. This package is the creation of Hadley Wickem, and it offers many advantageous features. For those of you familiar with Plyr, Dplyr is the next iteration, and it specifically focuses only on dataframes.
 Why You Should Use It Efficiency. Simplicity. Speed.
Dplyr provides tools to allow for increased speed, smaller utilization of memory, and efficiency/simplicity in writing functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/./about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Sarah Salter :). I am currently a Biostatistics graduate student at Johns Hopkins School of Public Health. I received my undergraduate training in Mathematical Science, and my graduate training in Biostatistics and Data Science. The past few years I have had the pleasure of working as a data scientist, medical research assistant and a teaching assistant during my time at Johns Hopkins University.
This blog is intended for data science enthusiasts, aspiring statistical ninjas, R-users, insatiable learners, and/or anyone that appreciates random pieces of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CodeRag</title>
      <link>/./coderag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./coderag/</guid>
      <description>Notes: This article originally appeared in CodeRag.
Code/Rag has always been more than just another online tech blog. We strive to be part of the tech community—serving an essential, fundamental look at what’s going on in the valley. It’s why our tagline is “Know Your Code.” We think a tech news publication should know the basics. Be the source. Get down to brass tacks. We can do that because we’re part of the very ecosystem we’re reporting on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>